$vRDNModName	Festive Flight
$vRDNMCMUnitSec	{0} seconds
$vRDNMCMUnitHours	{1} hours
$vRDNMCMUnitDeg	{0} degrees
$vRDNMCMSEHeader	Special Effects
$vRDNMCMSENoseGlow	Very shiny nose
$vRDNMCMSEHoofprints	Sparkly hoofprints
$vRDNMCMVanishAfter	Vanish after
$vRDNMCMPHeader	Performance
$vRDNMCMPSpeed	Movement Speed
$vRDNMCMAHeader	Advanced
$vRDNMCMAScan	Scan for orphaned objects
$vRDNMCMFOHeader	Flight options
$vRDNMCMFOEnableFlight	Enable Flight
$vRDNMCMFOEnableEL	Enable Emergency Landing
$vRDNMCMFOELD	 Emergency Landing delay
$vRDNMCMFOJumpToAscend	Hold Jump to gain altitude
$vRDNMCMFOJumpToFly	 Fly only while holding Jump
$vRDNMCMFOSmoothing	Flight Smoothing
$vRDNMCMFOMaxAscsent	Maximum angle of ascent
$vRDNMCMFOMaxDescent	Maximum angle of descent
$vRDNMCMFOUseStaticTO	Use Statics for takeoff
$vRDNMCMFOUseStaticAlways	Use Statics for all flight

$vRDNMCMHelpScan	Summoning Rudolph in versions prior to 1.05 may have left some harmless extra objects loaded in your save game. This option will scan for and remove them from nearby cells as you travel. This is enabled ONLY if you have upgraded from a previous version to 1.05 on THIS save game.
$vRDNMCMHelpRedNose	Enable/Disable the red glow on the nose.\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpHoofprints	Enable/Disable sparkly hoofprint effects, including sound effects. Disabling this may take some load off the script engine.\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpVanishAfter	After this many game hours, Rudolph will vanish. 0 disables this.\nDefault: 1.0
$vRDNMCMHelpSpeed	Speed setting for the reindeer. Lowering this gives your system more time to load new cells.\nDefault: 100%.
$vRDNMCMHelpFlightEnable	Disable this to remove all flight capability and disable all flight-related scripting. Don't disable this if you're in the air!\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpELEnable	While stopped in midair, aim the camera down to descend quickly. Useful for landing in narrow places.\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpELWait	How long you must look down while stopped before the emergency landing engages.\nDefault: 2 seconds.
$vRDNMCMHelpJumpEnable	Hold down the Jump button to climb regardless of camera position.\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpStaticTakeoffEnable	Use a static collision platforms when taking off. This makes the transition from the ground to the air much smoother with a minimum of camera bouncing. Disable this only if you have severe camera problems during takeoff.\nDefault: On
$vRDNMCMHelpStaticAlwaysEnable	Use static collision platforms for all flight. Use this ONLY if you find yourself frequently getting stuck in the air mid-flight, as it WILL cause the camera to behave oddly.\nDefault: Off
$vRDNMCMHelpMaxAscent	Maximum angle of ascent in degrees.\nDefault: 35.
$vRDNMCMHelpMaxDescent	Maximum angle of descent in degrees.\nDefault: 40.
$vRDNMCMHelpFlightSmoothing	How rapidly the reindeer can change direction vertically.\nLow values are more responsive. High values make the ride less bumpy.\nDefault: 2.
